slashgear.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - SlashGear

The following policy outlines the types of information that we gather about you and the way that way we use and don’t use this information.

With the introduction of the new European data protection laws, we wanted to explain SlashGear’s privacy and data storage policies. The data we collect is relatively limited, predominantly a record of your preferences under these privacy and data protection policies. We do not require user registration, and we use [anonymized IP addresses](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052?hl=en) for our analytics that can’t be linked with individual readers. We use third-party cookies for advertisers, all of whom are also GDPR compliant, and Disqus for site comments, which is again GDPR compliant.

By consenting to this privacy policy you are giving us permission to process your personal data specifically for the purposes identified. If we ever ask you for personal data, we’ll be clear as to why we do so, how the information is used, and how you can withdraw that data.

The information that we collect about our visitors falls into three general categories:

1\. Information You Provide to Us. We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply to us either on the SlashGear site, via e-mail contact form, or in any other way.

2\. Information that is Automatically Collected. We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate through the SlashGear site. For example, to enhance your experience at SlashGear, we use a standard feature found in browser software called a “cookie.” Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use our site, cookies help us track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of our site where you have entered preference information before. Another example of information that we automatically collect as you navigate our site is information about your computer’s connection to the Internet. This information allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on our site.

SlashGear includes links to other websites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through the Service, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

4\. Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web Site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)‘s consumer web site.

Questions on Privacy

If you have questions or concerns about the children’s privacy statement, the privacy practices of the SlashGear site, or your dealings with SlashGear, please [contact us](https://www.slashgear.com/contact/ "Contact Us").
